I am a heroine going slowly
I am a hundred years of war
I am Henry the eighth of England
with his back against the wall
I feel saintly in my bedroom
Your breath against my throat
I feel saintly in the supermarket
Slinging back a coke
You must think about me sometimes
Do you think of me at all?
I am not your saint here
I never chose to fall
Joan of Arc came after the show
Wearing neon, holding a microphone
Said: I am not a statue, I will never be a stone
I feel saintly in my bedroom
Her breath against my throat
I feel saintly on the battlefield,
Dancing across her moat
You must think about me sometimes
Do you think of me at all?
I am not your saint here
I never chose to fall
I am nothing wrong
I'm just sick of being someone else's song